joomunited.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy

##  [ Privacy policy](http://www.joomunited.com/privacy-policy)

JoomUnited is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the joomunited.com Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the JoomUnited website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information

JoomUnited collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. JoomUnited also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by JoomUnited. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by JoomUnited for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding the use of the JoomUnited Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through JoomUnited public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: JoomUnited does not read any of your private online communications.

JoomUnited encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from JoomUnited so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. JoomUnited is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the JoomUnited and JoomUnited family of Web sites.

### Use of your Personal Information

JoomUnited collects and uses your personal information to operate the JoomUnited Web site and deliver the services you have requested. JoomUnited also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from JoomUnited and its affiliates. JoomUnited may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

JoomUnited does not sell, rent or lease it's customer lists to third parties. JoomUnited may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, JoomUnited may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to JoomUnited, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

JoomUnited does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

JoomUnited keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within JoomUnited, in order to determine what JoomUnited services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within JoomUnited to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

JoomUnited Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on JoomUnited or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of JoomUnited; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of JoomUnited, or the public.

### Changes to this Statement

JoomUnited will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. JoomUnited encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how JoomUnited is protecting your information.
